George Brown College opened its doors in 1968, welcoming just over 2,000 students. In addition to programs in construction, early childhood education, dental services and the culinary arts — subjects we continue to teach — we once offered programs that might not be quite as relevant today, like signwriting and watchmaking. Believe it or not, we even prepared students for careers at sea through a marine engineering program.

Since then, our full-time student population has grown to around 30,000. People come to George Brown from across the Greater Toronto Area, the country and the world to develop the skills and gain the real-world experience needed to succeed in the workplace.

Since 2004, George Brown has more than doubled in size, broadened our international partnerships and increased our commitment to strengthening the cultural, economic and social fabric of Toronto.
