In this course students will learn the procedures, protocols and best practices that a DevOps engineer
brings to a workplace environment to increase productivity. Analyze and evaluate various developer
operation implementations available and implement hands-on work using industry standard toolkit.
Create solution to complex business problem by adhering to the core responsibilities of DevOpsStudents
will learn about data formats and types, including Extensible Markup Language (XML), JavaScript
Object Notation (JSON), Yaml Ain't Markup Language (YAML), and Yet Another Next Generation
(YANG), and their value in network automation, along with DevOps tools such as Ansible and Git.
